Seyfarth Shaw Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6337
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Teamsters Pension Material, 1959-1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Teamsters Pension Material, 1969-1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Teamsters Pension Material, 1976-1983 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Teamsters Pension Material, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Teamsters Pension Material, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Textile Workers, 1968-1986 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Typographical Union, 1979-1985 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Typographical Union Pension Material, 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- "T" Miscellaneous, 1979-1989 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- "T" Miscellaneous, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Upholsterers, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 24)